A Guide to the China Medical Board records, RG 2, Accession 2014:022, SG 2 FA1390
Rockefeller Archive Center
- China Medical Board Audiovisual materials, 1998-2002; 4; 5.47 Cubic Feet 10 legal boxes and 2 letter document boxes
  - Historical Record, Trip Reports, 2000 January-August (Box 82, Folder 799)
  - Historical Record, Trip Report, 2000 September 9-October 10 (Box 83, Folder 800)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, Thailand, and Beijing, 2000 January-February (Box 83, Folder 801)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, Beijing, Tianjin, and Shanghai, 2000 February (Box 83, Folder 802)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, Buchanan, Robert-Retirement Party, and China, 2000 February-March (Box 83, Folder 803)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, China, China Medical Board Visits, and Shand, Jane-Birthday, 2000 March-April, June (Box 83, Folder 804)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, Beijing, 2000 July (Box 83, Folder 805)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, Tibet and Hong Kong, 2000 July (Box 83, Folder 806)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, Emergency Landing, New Bay, Ontario, 2000 July 29 (Box 83, Folder 807)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, 2000 August, November-December (Box 84, Folder 808-809)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, Peking Union Medical College Society of Health Care Scholars, 2000 July 25 (Box 84, Folder 810)
  - Historical Record, Trip Reports, 2001 January-December (Box 84, Folder 811)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, China-Asia Trip, 2001 January-February (Box 84, Folder 812-816)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, Miscellaneous, 2001 (Box 84, Folder 817)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, Visits to China Medical Board and Institute for International Medical Education (IIME), 2001 April-June (Box 85, Folder 818)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, China Trip with Andrzej Wojtzcak, 2001 March-April (Box 85, Folder 819-822)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, Asia Trip, 2001 June 22-July 12 (Box 85, Folder 823-824)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, Asia Trip-Nepal, Tibet, and Mongolia, 2001 June 22-July 12 (Box 85, Folder 825-826)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, Asia Trip, 2001 June 22-July 12 (Box 86, Folder 827-830)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, China, Barcelona, and Lisbon, 2002 August 16-September 2 (Box 86, Folder 831)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, 2001 July-August (Box 86, Folder 832)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, China Trip, 2001 October 14-November 3 (Box 86, Folder 833-836)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, China Medical Board Meeting and Dinner, 2001 December 10-11 (Box 87, Folder 837)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, Jiujiang City Weekend, 2001 October 26-28 (Box 87, Folder 838)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, Human Subjects Conference, 2001 October 20 (Box 87, Folder 839)
  - Historical Record, Trip Reports, 2002 January-December (Box 87, Folder 840)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, China-Thailand Trip, 2002 January 31-February 21 (Box 87, Folder 841)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, Asia-China Trip, 2002 April (Box 87, Folder 842-843)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, Board of Trustees Meeting, 2002 June 1-5 (Box 87, Folder 844-845)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, China Trip, 2002 July 1-12, August 13-20 (Box 87, Folder 846-847)
  - Historical Record, Photographs, China Trip, 2002 August 13-October 23 (Box 88, Folder 848-854)
  - Ranuch's Retirement, Airlangga Award, 1992 January; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 13000)
  - The CMC Project (Chinese-MedNet Consortium), 1997; 5 minutes; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 13001)
  - 1st CMC Teleconference, USA-China Discussion on Cardiovascular Disease, 1997; 105 minutes; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 13002)
  - The Computerized Pupil, VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 13003)
  - CME Report, 1992 June-1996 October; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 13004)
    Open for research. Digital access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instructionn.
  - Peking Union Medical College Hospital, VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 13005)
  - Tibet Medical College Workshop. Asian System, 1993 March; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 13006)
  - Report on the Progress of the Program of Higher Education Development, Faculty of Nursing, Xian Medical University, 1998 January, April; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 13007)
  - Community Medicine: School of Medicine Airlangga University at Nganjuk, VHS (PAL) (Box 2, Tape AV 13008)
  - Community Medicine, School of Medicine Airlangga University at Nganjuk, VHS (PAL) (Box 2, Tape AV 13009)
  - (Title in an Asian Language), VHS (PAL) (Box 2, Tape AV 13010)
  - China Medical Board Visit to Kediri Airlangga Community Teaching Programme, 1990 January 17; VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 13011)
  - China Medical Board Visit to Kediri Airlangga Community Teaching Programme, 1990 January 17; Betamax (Box 2, Tape AV 13012)
  - Xian Medical College/University, Progress Report, 1998 January; VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 13013)
  - Tibet Workshop, 1993 March; VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 13014)
  - University of Alabama at Birmingham, Xian Medical University, Graduation Ceremony, 1989; VHS (Box 2, Tape AV 13015)